http://www.uswca.org/privacy-policy

Circuit Events
What is the USWCA Circuit Event?
Privacy policy
This is the privacy policy of USWCA. This document explains USWCA policies for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information.
The Information We Collect
USWCA collects information by various methods including information actively provided by its lead providers, its customers, and information arising from customer surveys and general feedback.
The types of personal information we collect include name, contact information, identification information and credit information. Credit card information is used for billing purposes only. We may record calls to or from our sales/customer service representatives for purposes of accuracy, performance reviews, training, and general quality assurance.
How We Use This Information
This information is used to aid in the provision of our various products and services, including customer service, accounting, billing, collections, and the marketing of other products services. USWCA may use aggregate or anonymous information for various uses for itself and third parties.
USWCA does not share personal information with any third parties except as disclosed in this policy. USWCA may provide personal information to USWCA subcontractors and professional advisers (which shall be bound by privacy obligations) to assist USWCA uses disclosed herein.
Security
Personal information is stored in a combination of paper and electronic files. They are protected by security measures appropriate to the nature of the information.
Accessing Information
Individuals may review their personal information contained in USWCA files by contacting the USWCA privacy officer. If an individual believes that any of their personal information is inaccurate, we will make appropriate corrections.
Cookies
Cookies are used by USWCA for the convenience of our users. Cookies automatically authenticate the user. A user can access the USWCA Web site with the cookie feature turned off; however, in doing so they may find themselves challenged for username and password information on multiple occasions. USWCA also uses cookies to track user's visits and uses that information to improve the user's experience.
Links
The USWCA Web site may contain links to information at other Web sites. When you click on one of these links, you are moving to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.
General
USWCA may amend this policy from time to time. If such amendments affect how USWCA uses or discloses personal information already held by USWCA in a material way, USWCA will obtain consent.
Notwithstanding the general terms of this policy, the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information may be made outside of the terms herein to the extent provided for in any applicable privacy or other legislation in effect from time to time.
USWCA may disclose personal information to another entity purchasing (including for diligence purposes prior to purchase) the assets of USWCA, provided that entity abides by this or a similar privacy policy.
© United States Women's Curling Association  All rights reserved.
